<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GraphWiz</title>
    <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GraphWiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 -0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://graphwizai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hubs Learning Rooms</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs-learning-rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs-learning-rooms/</guid>
      <description>This virtual space showcases the power and accessibility of Hubs, a virtual reality (VR) platform enabling users to create and join shared 3D environments for socializing, collaboration, and immersive experiences. Users can interact via customizable avatars directly from their web browsers, eliminating the need for plugins or downloads. GraphWiz’s new Hubs instance provides a personalized and engaging environment for connection, communication, and exploration within the virtual realm, reflecting the company’s commitment to innovative digital spaces and the growing popularity of virtual collaboration tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immersive WebXR Experience</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/immersive-webxr-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/immersive-webxr-experience/</guid>
      <description>This immersive WebXR experience is designed to introduce newcomers to the world of Virtual Reality. The experience is accessible via a single click from a WebXR-enabled browser. The application represents a good demonstration for comfortable VR accessibility. It utilizes the WebXR technology, a collaborative effort from a consortium including Google, Microsoft, and Mozilla, among other industry leaders. This interface replaces the outdated WebVR 1.1 standard, which suffered from various limitations and was restricted to Virtual Reality applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/ai/</guid>
      <description>What does it even mean? Artificial Intelligence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ops</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/ops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/ops/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/workshops/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
