<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GraphWiz</title>
    <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GraphWiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 -0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://graphwizai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hubs Learning Rooms</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs-learning-rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs-learning-rooms/</guid>
      <description>GraphWiz has launched its own Hubs instance: https://hubs.tobias-weiss.org/
This virtual space showcases the power and accessibility of Hubs, a virtual reality (VR) platform enabling users to create and join shared 3D environments for socializing, collaboration, and immersive experiences. Users can interact via customizable avatars directly from their web browsers, eliminating the need for plugins or downloads. GraphWiz’s new Hubs instance provides a personalized and engaging environment for connection, communication, and exploration within the virtual realm, reflecting the company’s commitment to innovative digital spaces and the growing popularity of virtual collaboration tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Room Environments</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs_experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/hubs_experiments/</guid>
      <description>How do new, exciting and at the same time challenging technologies, such as virtual reality, find their way into university teaching?  Our paper describes an interdisciplinary project that addresses precisely this question. Our goal is to represent the periodic table of elements as a network of virtual environments in which each element has its own space. A separate learning environment should be designed for each element, which is enriched with information about the elements (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immersive WebXR Experience</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/immersive-webxr-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/xr/immersive-webxr-experience/</guid>
      <description>TLDR; The official WebXR Demo Instance is down. GraphWiz now hosts a private version of it: https://tobias-weiss.org/hello-webxr/
Mozilla’s immersive WebXR experience, designed to introduce newcomers to the world of Virtual Reality, is now hosted by GraphWiz. The experience is accessible via a single click from a WebXR-enabled browser. The application represents a significant advancement in VR accessibility. It utilizes the WebXR technology, a collaborative effort from a consortium including Google, Microsoft, and Mozilla, among other industry leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://graphwizai.github.io/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphwizai.github.io/ai/</guid>
      <description>We provide specialized AI coaching and consulting services, focusing on the strategic integration of cutting-edge AI technologies to enhance business operations and customer engagement. We leverage our expertise in AI agents, specifically utilizing the power of LLMs and knowledge graphs to deliver tailored solutions. We go beyond simply recommending AI tools; we guide businesses through the entire process, from identifying opportunities for AI integration to developing and implementing customized strategies. We possess extensive experience in designing and deploying AI-powered systems, including conversational agents for virtual commerce and other interactive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
